ctflames.com 2016-10-17

# Privacy Policy – Connecticut Flames – CTFlames.com

**Information CTFlames.com May Collect**

CTFlames.com, may collect personal information about you when you send an email to admin/owner of CTFlames.com or submit any contact form on CTFlames.com or Signup as Subscriber to register on CTFlames.com to comment or participate in public discussions. CTFlames.com may obtain this personal information (which may include your Name, Email Address, City Name, IP Address, Post Code, Postal Address) in any of the following ways:

  * you provide it on the CTFlames.com registration page;
  * you provide it on CTFlames.com Email/Newsleter/Rss Feed Subscription forms;
  * you provide it on the CTFlames.com using contact form;
  * you provide it during email communications or inquires; or
  * CTFlames.com obtain it to complete your requested information or keep records of your correspondences.

**How Your Information Is Used**

CTFlames.com does not disclose your personal information to anyone for marketing purposes. CTFlames.com discloses your personal information only to those service providers, affiliated and non-affiliated, who need the information to respond to your inquiries and/or to service and maintain your account. In addition, CTFlames.com may be required to disclose your personal information to government agencies and other regulatory bodies (for example, for spam or cyber crime reporting purposes or to report suspicious hacking attempts or misuse of CTFlames.com website/blog). The affiliated and non-affiliated service providers who receive your personal information may use it to:

  * process your requested information (For Example WordPress.com for New posts Subscription Alerts);
  * provide you with detailed information regrading your sign-up or registration information;
  * mail your password reset requests or stats of any tracking; and
  * enhance your browsing experience.

These service providers provide services at CTFlames.com’s direction and include fulfillment companies, printing and mailing facilities.

Under their agreements with CTFlames.com, these service providers are required to keep your personal information confidential and to use it only for providing the contractually required services.

**Security of Your Information**

TFI protects the personal information you provide against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, destruction, loss or misuse. Your personal information is protected by physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in accordance with federal and state standards. These safeguards include appropriate procedures for access and use of electronic data, provisions for the secure transmission of sensitive personal information on the CTFlames.com’s website, and telephone system authentication procedures.

**Changes in CTFlames.com Privacy Policy**

CTFlames.com periodically reviews this Privacy Policy and its related practices and procedures. You will be notified of any material amendments to this Privacy Policy.

**Notice About Online Privacy**

The personal information that you provide through the CTFlames.com website is handled in the same way as the personal information that you provide by any other means, as described above. This section of the notice gives you additional information about the way in which personal information that is obtained online is handled.

**Online Registration and  Account Access**

When you visit the CTFlames.com website, you can go to pages that are open to the general public or log onto protected pages to register in the CTFlames.com, access information about your account, or conduct certain actions on your account. Once you register on CTFlames.com, access to the secure pages of the CTFlames.com website is permitted only after you have created a User ID and Password by supplying your Name and email address. The User ID and Password must be supplied each time you want to access your account information online. This information serves to verify your identity.

When you enter personal data into the CTFlames.com website (including your Name and email address and your password) to enroll or access your account online, you will log into secure pages where CTFlames.com use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol for protecting information.

To use this section of the CTFlames.com website you need a browser that supports encryption and dynamic Web page construction.

If you provide personal information by sending an email via contact form on the CTFlames.com website, a record of the other information i.e Your browser version, your Location IP Address, your referring page that you have used while on the site is retained by the CTFlames.com.

**Other Personal Information Provided by You on the CTFlames.com Website**

If you decide not to enroll online and you want to request CTFlames.com articles and posts to be mailed to you, or you want to subscribe to the CTFlames.com e-mail newsletter, you can click on newsletter sign-up button on CTFlames.com website to provide your name and e-mail address, respectively. The personal information that you provide on that page of the CTFlames.com will be stored and used to contact you more effectively. Although that Subscribe of the CTFlames.com website does not use SSL encryption protocol, your information will be safeguarded in accordance with federal and state privacy laws and industry norms.

**The CTFlames.com Cares about Your Privacy**

_CTFlames.com_ use cookies on the website to measure marketing results for the _CTFlames.com_. This process renders all visitors to the _CTFlames.com_ website anonymous and will not personally identify you.

**Obtaining Additional Information**

If  you have questions regarding CTFlames.com Privacy Policy you can always send an email directly to nick(@)CTFlames.com or use contact page to fill a contact form.
